What is the biggest misconception you feel people have about the Caribbean diaspora?
Oh, it is just wine and I don't know.
To be serious, I think that's looking at us as a monolith, that we only speak a certain way, dance a certain way and not realizing just like how multicultural the Caribbean is.
Some of the things that we love about the Caribbean reflect our diversity, even the stereotype, the smoking weed endless.
That comes from our Indian indentured laborers who came in after slavery.
Roti, same thing, come from some of our biggest artists like Shensia.
She's a Chinese Jamaican heritage.
What is one thing you said in this episode that you would stand 10 toes down on?
Within the Caribbean story and the Black American story that we are so deeply interconnected in a positive way.
Our histories are so intertwined that we should be celebrating that and not fighting.